{
  "type": "audio2hira",
  "level": "YOUON",
  "questions": [
    { "prompt": "きゃ", "answer": "きゃ" },
    { "prompt": "きゅ", "answer": "きゅ" },
    { "prompt": "きょ", "answer": "きょ" },
    { "prompt": "しゃ", "answer": "しゃ" },
    { "prompt": "しゅ", "answer": "しゅ" },
    { "prompt": "しょ", "answer": "しょ" },
    { "prompt": "ちゃ", "answer": "ちゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ちゅ", "answer": "ちゅ" },
    { "prompt": "ちょ", "answer": "ちょ" },
    { "prompt": "にゃ", "answer": "にゃ" },
    { "prompt": "にゅ", "answer": "にゅ" },
    { "prompt": "にょ", "answer": "にょ" },
    { "prompt": "ひゃ", "answer": "ひゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ひゅ", "answer": "ひゅ" },
    { "prompt": "ひょ", "answer": "ひょ" },
    { "prompt": "みゃ", "answer": "みゃ" },
    { "prompt": "みゅ", "answer": "みゅ" },
    { "prompt": "みょ", "answer": "みょ" },
    { "prompt": "りゃ", "answer": "りゃ" },
    { "prompt": "りゅ", "answer": "りゅ" },
    { "prompt": "りょ", "answer": "りょ" },
    { "prompt": "ぎゃ", "answer": "ぎゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ぎゅ", "answer": "ぎゅ" },
    { "prompt": "ぎょ", "answer": "ぎょ" },
    { "prompt": "じゃ", "answer": "じゃ" },
    { "prompt": "じゅ", "answer": "じゅ" },
    { "prompt": "じょ", "answer": "じょ" },
    { "prompt": "びゃ", "answer": "びゃ" },
    { "prompt": "びゅ", "answer": "びゅ" },
    { "prompt": "びょ", "answer": "びょ" },
    { "prompt": "ぴゃ", "answer": "ぴゃ" },
    { "prompt": "ぴゅ", "answer": "ぴゅ" },
    { "prompt": "ぴょ", "answer": "ぴょ" }
  ]
}
